<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<bank xmlns="https://checkit.clontz.org" version="0.2">
    <title>MATH 144</title>
    <slug>math-144</slug>
    <url>https://checkit.clontz.org</url>
    <outcomes>
        <outcome>
            <title>Terms and factors</title>
            <slug>EX1</slug>
            <path>outcomes/EX1</path>
            <description>
I can identify terms and factors. I can combine like terms and factor out common factors.
            </description>
        </outcome>
        <outcome>
            <title>Functions</title>
            <slug>F1</slug>
            <path>outcomes/F/F1</path>
            <description>
I can use function notation, find and simplify the output of a function given an input, and find an input that produces a given output; I can do this for functions given by a formula, a table, and a graph.
            </description>
        </outcome>
        <outcome>
            <title>Average rate of change</title>
            <slug>F2</slug>
            <path>outcomes/F/F2</path>
            <description>
I can find the average rate of change (AROC) of a function on a given interval. In an applied context, I can state the units and interpret the real-world meaning of the AROC.
            </description>
        </outcome>
        <outcome>
            <title>Linear functions</title>
            <slug>F3</slug>
            <path>outcomes/F/F3</path>
            <description>
I can find the slope of a linear function and find equations for the function in point-slope and slope-intercept form.
            </description>
        </outcome>
<!-- Chapter C -->
        <outcome>
            <title>Generating circular functions</title>
            <slug>C1</slug>
            <path>outcomes/C/C1</path>
            <description>
I can generate an accurate, labeled graph of a circular function given appropriate information about the circle being traversed, and describe key features of the function.
            </description>
        </outcome>
        <outcome>
            <title>Transforming circular functions</title>
            <slug>C2</slug>
            <path>outcomes/C/C2</path>
            <description>
I can find the amplitude, period, and midline of a transformed version of the basic sine or cosine function; and I can find the formulas for transformed versions of the basic sine or cosine function.
            </description>
        </outcome>
<!-- Chapter E -->
        <outcome>
            <title>Fitting exponential functions</title>
            <slug>E1</slug>
            <path>outcomes/E/E1</path>
            <description>
I can find the formula for an exponential function given two data points.
            </description>
        </outcome>
        <outcome>
            <title>Features of exponential functions</title>
            <slug>E2</slug>
            <path>outcomes/E/E2</path>
            <description>
I can describe the long-term behavior of an exponential function or a transformed version of an exponential function. I can tell whether the function is increasing, decreasing, concave up, or concave down.
            </description>
        </outcome>
        <outcome>
            <title>Using exponential and logarithmic expressions</title>
            <slug>E3</slug>
            <path>outcomes/E/E3</path>
            <description>
I can solve equations involving exponential and logarithmic expressions. I can apply the properties of exponential and logarithmic functions to simplify expressions.
            </description>
        </outcome>
<!-- Chapter T -->
        <outcome>
            <title>Sine, cosine, and tangent</title>
            <slug>T1</slug>
            <path>outcomes/T/T1</path>
            <description>
I can find the values of sine, cosine, and tangent at special points on the unit circle or for angles in a right triangle with labeled sides.
            </description>
        </outcome>
        <outcome>
            <title>Arcsine, arccosine, and arctangent</title>
            <slug>T3</slug>
            <path>outcomes/T/T3</path>
            <description>
I can compute the values of the arcsine, arccosine, and arctangent functions for inputs arising from the unit circle or a labeled right triangle.
            </description>
        </outcome>
    </outcomes>
</bank>